Register of the Commission for Relief in Belgium Records, 1914-1930
Hoover Institution Archives
- NEW YORK OFFICE STATE CORRESPONDENCE, 1914-1919
  - New York
    - Cities
      - New York City
        - American Steamship Association (Folder 10)
        - American Lead Pencil Company (Folder 11)
        - American Line (Folder 12)
        - American Lithographic Company (Folder 13)
        - American National Red Cross (Folder 14)
        - American Press Association (Folder 15)
        - Andrew Mills and Sons (Folder 16)
        - Appleton, Katherine Todd (Folder 17)
        - Armour and Company (Folder 18)
        - Associated Press (Folder 19)
        - Austin Nichols and Company
          - 1914-1916 (Folder 20)
          - 1917-1918 (Box 275, Folder 1)
        - Barber and Company (Folder 2)
        - Belgian Bureau (Folder 3)
        - Belgian Kiddies Limited (Folder 4)
        - Belgian Relief Committee (re: in cooperation with the Rockefeller Foundation) (Folder 5)
        - Belgian Relief Fund
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 6)
          - 1916-1918 (Folder 7)
        - Chamber of Commerce (Folder 8)
        - Children of American's Army of Relief (Folder 9)
        - Christian Herald Relief Fund (Folder 10)
        - Coffin, C. A. (Folder 11)
        - Colliers Weekly (Folder 12)
        - Columbia University (Folder 13)
        - Committee of Mercy (Folder 14)
        - Cudahy Packing Company (Folder 15)
        - Cuddihy, R. J. (re: Literary Digest) (Folder 16)
        - Cutting, R. Fulton (Folder 17)
        - Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Rail Road Company (Box 276, Folder 1)
        - Deloitte, Plender, Griffiths and Company (Folder 2)
        - Dollar Christmas Fund for Belgian Children (Folder 3)
        - Dyer, Arthur (Folder 4)
        - Equitable Office Building Corporation (Folder 5)
        - Erie Railroad (re: Freight Claim) (Folder 6)
        - Federal Composition and Paint Company, Ltd. (Folder 7)
        - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Folder 8)
        - Fidelity and Deposit Company of Maryland (Folder 9)
        - Finley, John H. (Box 277, Folder 1)
        - Fitzhenry, J. J. (Folder 2)
        - France. Haut Commissariat de la Republique Francaise aux Etats-Unis (Folder 3)
        - Furness, Withy and Company, Ltd. (Folder 4)
        - Guaranty Trust and Company
          - General
            - 1914-1915 (Folder 5)
            - 1916-1918 (Folder 6)
          - Norwegian Kroners Account (Folder 7)
          - Swedish Kroners Account (Folder 8)
        - Hemphill, Alexander (Folder 9)
        - Henry Liska and Company (Box 278, Folder 1)
        - Hermann, A. S. (Folder 2)
        - Hero Land Bazaar (Folder 3)
        - Hudson Auto Lamp Works (Folder 4)
        - J. D. McCarthy Company (Folder 5)
        - J. H. Bertine and Company, Inc. (Folder 6)
        - Knickerbocker Ice Company (Folder 7)
        - Libby, McNeill and Libby (Folder 8)
        - Literary Digest (Folder 9)
        - Lucey, John F. (Folder 10)
        - Mail and Express Job Print (Folder 11)
        - Mali, Pierre
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 12)
          - 1917-1918 (Folder 13)
        - National Allied Relief Committee (Folder 14)
        - National City Bank (Box 279, Folder 1)
        - National Surety Company (Folder 2)
        - Norton and Lilly Company
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 3)
          - 1915 (Folder 4-6)
          - 1916 (Folder 7)
          - 1917-1918 (Box 280, Folder 1)
        - Patriotic Service League (Folder 2)
        - Phoenix Ribbon and Carbon Company (Folder 3)
        - Polish Victim Relief Fund (Folder 4)
        - Postal Telegraph Cable Company (Folder 5)
        - Prest-O-Lite Company (Folder 6)
        - Remington Typewriter Company (Folder 7)
        - Rockefeller Foundation (Folder 8)
        - Rocky Mountain Club (Folder 9)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore (Folder 10)
        - Sadeleer, Louis de (Folder 11)
        - Signode System, Inc. (Folder 12)
        - Thomas Cook and Son (Folder 13)
        - United States. Food Administration (Box 281, Folder 1)
        - United States. Shipping Board (Folder 2)
        - Vacation War Relief Committee (Folder 3)
        - Western Union Telegraph Company
          - 1915-1916 (Folder 4)
          - 1917-1918 (Folder 5)
        - Wheat Export Company (Folder 6)
        - Whittaker, L. R.
        - Wilcox, Peck and Hughes (Folder 7)
        - Wilson and Company (Folder 8)
        - Wisconsin Condensed Milk Company (Folder 9)
      - Newburgh (Box 282, Folder 1)
      - Oneida (Folder 2)
      - Oyster Bay (Folder 3)
      - Plattsburg (Folder 4)
      - Poughkeepsie (Folder 5)
      - Purdy Station (Folder 6)
      - Rochester
        - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 7)
        - Rochester Chamber of Commerce (Folder 8)
        - Rochester Committee (Folder 9)
      - Rome (Folder 10)
      - Schenectady (Folder 11)
      - Spuyten Duyvil (Folder 12)
      - Syracuse
        - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 13)
        - Syracuse Committee (Folder 14)
      - Troy (Folder 15)
      - Utica
        - General (Folder 16)
        - Utica Committee (Folder 17)
      - White Plains (Folder 18)
      - Zonkers (Folder 19)
  - North Carolina
    - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 20)
    - Cities
      - Asheville (Folder 21)
      - Greensboro (Folder 22)
      - Greensville (Folder 23)
      - Raleigh (Folder 24)
    - Committees - North Carolina Committee of the Commission for Relief of Belgium (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
  - North Dakota
    - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 3)
    - North Dakota State Committee (Folder 4)
  - Ohio
    - General
      - General
        - 1914-1915 (Folder 5)
        - 1916-1918 (Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1914-1915 (Folder 7)
    - Cities
      - Canton (Folder 8)
      - Cincinnati
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Cincinnati Committee (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - Cleveland
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Garfield, James R., Mrs. (Folder 3)
      - Columbus (Folder 4)
      - Dayton (Folder 5)
      - Springfield (Folder 6)
      - Toledo
        - General (Folder 7)
        - Libbey, Edward Drummond (Folder 8)
        - Sheppy, Marshall (Folder 9)
    - Committees - Ohio State Committee (Folder 10-11)
  - Oklahoma (Box 285)
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 1)
    - Cities
      - Oklahoma City (Folder 2)
      - Okmulgee (Folder 3)
      - Tulsa
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Tulsa Committee (re: Mary Jane Bennett) (Folder 5)
    - Committees - Oklahoma State Committee (Folder 6)
  - Oregon
    - General
      - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1914-1915 (Folder 8)
    - Cities - Portland
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Belgian Children's Food Fund (re: S. L. Eddy) (Folder 10)
      - Portland Committee (re: W. B. Ayer) (Folder 11)
    - Committees - Oregon State Committee (Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania
    - General
      - 1914-1916 (Folder 13)
      - 1917-1918 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Cities
      - Bryn Mawr (Folder 2)
      - Butler (Folder 3)
      - Chambersburg (Folder 4)
      - Germantown (Folder 5)
      - Greensburg (Folder 6)
      - Harrisburg (Folder 7)
      - Lancaster (Folder 8)
      - Mill Hall (Folder 9)
      - Oil City (Folder 10)
      - Philadelphia
        - 1914-1916 (Folder 11)
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 12)
      - Pittsburgh (Box 287)
        - General (Folder 1)
        - American Physicians for Aid of Belgian Physicians (Folder 2)
        - Pittsburgh Committee (Folder 3)
      - Point Marion (Folder 4)
      - Pottsville (Folder 5)
      - Punxsutawney (Folder 6)
      - Reading (Folder 7)
      - Scranton (Folder 8)
      - Titusville (Folder 9)
      - Wilkinsburg (Folder 10)
      - Wilks-Barre (Folder 11)
      - Williamsport (Folder 12)
    - Committees and organizations
      - Belgian Children's Relief Committee of Pennsylvania (Folder 13)
      - Belgian Relief Committee of the Emergency Aid (re: Mrs. Bayard Henry) (Box 288, Folder 1)
      - Berks County Committee (re: Mary Archer) (Folder 2-3)
      - Pennsylvania Committee for C.R.B. (re: Albert Cross)
        - 1914 (Folder 4)
        - 1915-1916 (Folder 5)
        - 1917-1918 (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania Committee of Women (re: Mrs. Bayard Henry) (Folder 2)
      - Queen of the Belgians Fund. Clippings from The Ladies' Home Journal about the Queen of the Belgians Fund (Folder 3)
  - Rhode Island
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 4)
    - Cities
      - East Greenwich (Folder 5)
      - Newport
        - General (Folder 6)
        - Webster, Hamilton, Mrs. (Folder 7)
        - Wetmore, George Peabody (Folder 8)
      - Pawtucket (Folder 9)
      - Providence (Folder 10)
    - Committees and organizations
      - Children's Tin Box Fund (Folder 11)
      - Rhode Island State Committee (Folder 12)
  - South Carolina (Box 290)
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 1)
    - Cities
      - Aiken (Folder 2)
      - Charleston
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Carolina Company. Compilation of donations received by the Carolina Company from various towns and cities in South Carolina. Arranged according to towns and showing articles shipped out per S/S St. Helena (Folder 4)
      - Columbia (Folder 5)
    - Committees - South Carolina State Committee (Folder 6)
  - South Dakota
    - General
      - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 7)
      - Reports, 1916-1917 (Folder 8)
    - Cities - Yankton (Folder 9)
    - Committees - South Dakota State Committee (re: George R. Douthit) (Folder 10)
  - Tennessee (Box 291)
    - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 1)
    - Cities
      - Chattanooga (re: H. Clay Evans) (Folder 2)
      - Knoxville (Folder 3)
      - Memphis (Folder 4)
      - Nashville (Folder 5)
    - Committees - Tennessee Committee of Belgian Relief (re: Della Dortch) (Folder 6)
  - Texas
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 7)
    - Cities
      - Austin
        - General (Folder 8)
        - Colquitt, O. B. (Folder 9)
      - Dallas (Folder 10)
      - Galveston (Folder 11)
      - Houston (Folder 12)
      - San Antonio (Folder 13)
    - Committees and organizations
      - Texas Cantonments Clothing Campaign (re: Curtis Hill) (Folder 14)
      - Texas State Committee for C.R.B. (re: Mrs. Fred Fleming) (Folder 15)
  - Utah
    - General, 1918 (Folder 16)
    - Salt Lake City (Folder 17)
  - Vermont (Box 292)
    - General
      - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1914-1915 (Folder 2)
    - Cities - Burlington (Folder 3)
    - Committees - Vermont Committee of C.R.B. (Folder 4)
  - Virginia
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 5)
    - Cities
      - Front Royal (Folder 6)
      - Norfolk (Folder 7)
      - Richmond
        - General (Folder 8)
        - Barber and Company (Folder 9)
        - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company (Folder 10)
        - Dunlop Mills (Folder 11)
      - Roanoke
        - General (Folder 12)
        - Bennett, James M. (Folder 13)
    - Committees - Virginia Commission on Belgian Relief (re: H. M. Boykin) (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Washington
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 2)
    - Cities
      - Seattle
        - General (Folder 3)
        - Hoover Fund for Washington State (Folder 4)
      - Spokane
        - General (Folder 5)
        - Serruys, M. (Folder 6)
      - Tacoma
        - General (Folder 7)
        - Tacoma Committee (Folder 8)
    - Committees - Washington Committee of C.R.B. (re: Mrs. B. C. Beck and Thomas Burke) (Folder 9)
  - West Virginia
    - General, 1915-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Pennsboro (Folder 11)
    - Salem (Folder 12)
    - South Charleston (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Wisconsin
    - General, 1914-1918 (Folder 2)
    - Cities
      - Denmark (Folder 3)
      - Johnson Creek (Folder 4)
      - Madison (Folder 5)
      - Milwaukee
        - General (Folder 6)
        - L. Teweles Seed Company (Folder 7)
        - Milwaukee Committee of C.R.B. (Folder 8)
      - Watertown (Folder 9)
      - Williams Bay (re: Mrs. E. B. Frost) (Folder 10)
    - Committees - Wisconsin Committee of C.R.B. (re: E. P. Arpin) (Folder 11)
  - Wyoming
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Cheyenne (Folder 13)
- NEW YORK OFFICE GENERAL FILES, 1914-1918
  - Activity reports of the Organization Department (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - Albert I, King of the Belgians, 1875-1934 (Folder 2)
      - Bates, Lindon, Jr. (Folder 4)
      - Bates, Lindon W. (Folder 3)
      - Berton, S. Reading (Folder 5)
      - Brinton, Willard C. (Folder 6)
      - British American War Relief Fund (Folder 7)
      - Broenniman, E. G. (Folder 8)
      - Bush Terminal Warehouse (re: Petraeus, P.) (Folder 9)
      - Gray, Prentiss N. (re: his personal file) (Folder 10)
      - John S. Sills and Sons (Folder 11)
      - Hobbs, Henry H. (Folder 12)
      - Honnold, William L. (re: his personal file) (Folder 13)
      - Irwin, Will (Box 296, Folder 1)
      - Lucey, J. F. (Folder 2)
      - Martin, Frederick (Folder 3)
      - Presidential Advisory Committee (Folder 4)
      - Reynolds, John B. (Folder 5)
      - Sherman, Roger (re: S.S. Samland) (Folder 6)
      - Van Voorhies, Eugene F. (Folder 7)
      - White, John Beaver (Folder 8)
    - Organization Department
      - General - Appeal to Governors of States (Folder 9)
      - Bakers, George Barr. Includes letters during his visit to the Pope Archbishop Keane in Rome (Folder 10)
      - Cochems, E. B. (Folder 11-12)
      - Davis, Jefferson D. (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - Sasseen, David E. (Folder 2)
      - Stacy, Harwood T. (Folder 3)
    - Publicity Department - Thompson, C. S. (Folder 4)
    - Textile Department - Megraw, Robert H. (Folder 5)
  - Estimated costs of relief programs
    - General
      - Belgium and Northern France (Folder 6)
      - United States - New York (Folder 7)
    - Dunkirk and Rotterdam programs (Folder 8)
  - Form letters and letter heads (Folder 9)
  - Guidelines and suggestions for individual state organization representing the C.R.B. (Folder 10)
  - Instructions for processing incoming and outgoing mail and cables (Folder 11)
  - Interoffice memoranda
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Cranston, Mr. (Folder 13)
    - Fletcher, John D. (Folder 14)
    - Gray, Prentiss N. (Folder 15)
    - Grosser, Miss (Folder 16)
    - Gutterson, H. L. (Folder 17)
    - Healy, James A. (Folder 18)
    - Lawrence, John S. (Folder 19)
    - Merritt, Ralph P. (Folder 20)
    - Mitchell, Sidney A. (Folder 21)
    - O'Brien, Frederick (Folder 22)
    - Rickard, Edgar (Folder 23)
    - Sherman, Roger (Folder 24)
    - Walcott, F. C. (Folder 25)
    - Whitmarsh, Theodore F. (Folder 26)
  - Lists (Box 298)
    - Delegates in Northern France (Folder 1)
    - Donations (Folder 2)
    - Selected names from the 1917 social register. Compiled by Commercial Dispatch Addressing and Delivery Company (Folder 3)
    - Subscriptions (Folder 4)
  - Minutes of meeting in Mr. Davis' office (Folder 5)
  - Payment statements
    - Benham and Boyesen, Inc. (Folder 6)
    - Bogert and Greenbank (Folder 7)
    - Borden's Condensed Milk Company (Folder 8)
    - Bovie, C. (Folder 9)
    - Burrelle's Press Clipping Bureau (Folder 10)
    - Bush Terminal Company (Folder 11)
    - United States. Shipping Board (re: Emergency Fleet Corporation) (Folder 12)
  - Personnel records. See also Lists
    - General. Includes lists of names of staff in the New York Office with their job titles and job description. Also includes reference letters, information about salary, and other miscellaneous letters of employment with the C.R.B. (Folder 13)
    - Baylis, Charles T. (Folder 14)
  - Purchasing records (Box 299)
    - Approval invoices of purchases (Folder 1)
    - Confirmation statements of purchases (Folder 2)
    - Remittance blanks (Folder 3)
    - Requisition forms for supplies (Folder 4)
  - Shipping records
    - Estimated figures for net cargo shipments from U.S. and Canadian ports in long tons (Folder 5)
    - List of Norwegian Ships in service (Folder 6)
    - Shipping instructions
      - Cooperating committees and organizations. Includes the Women's Section of the C.R.B., other committees collecting foodstuffs and the American Commission for Relief in Belgium (Folder 7)
      - National organization (Folder 8)
    - Steamer schedules (Folder 9)
    - Time charters (Folder 10)
    - Miscellany. Includes lists of steamers at port, cargoes landed at discharged ports, cargoes in transit to discharge, steamers nearing port, steamers chartered to load in America, correspondence, and other miscellaneous materials relating to shipping operations (Folder 11)
  - Status reports (in metric tons)
    - General. Statistics for various commodities. Also includes figures per capita and some shipping schedules (Folder 12)
    - Dunkirk and Rotterdam relief programs (Folder 13)
  - Subject file
    - American Fraternity of the C.R.B. Directory of the American members of the C.R.B. (Folder 14)
    - Barley for brewing. Requesting information about the alleged shipments of barley into Belgium for brewing (Folder 15)
    - Belgian Babies Forget-Me-Not-Day fund raising campaign. Reports, correspondence, lists of names of committees and volunteers, post cards, and some printed matter (Folder 16)
    - C.R.B. Bulletin. Correspondence, data and suggestions (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Cereals. Study of a plan for shipping and packaging cereals to France during 1917-1918 (Folder 2)
    - Customs. Correspondence from various custom offices, the Internal Revenue Office, and shipping companies (Folder 3)
    - Foodstuffs. Correspondence and analysis concerning various methods of shipping vegetables and other foodstuffs to Belgium. Also includes regulations and guidelines for food companies to package food supplies in a safe manner and ensure the foodstuffs stay in good condition during shipment (Folder 4)
    - Germany. Letter from the Imperial German Embassy granting Edgar A. Mowrer free and unhindered travel from Germany to Belgium. Also includes reports from two English Rhodes scholars on the present situation in Germany (Folder 5)
    - Rice. Cross references (Folder 6)
    - Rotten foodstuffs. Consists mainly of correspondence regarding Mr. Alfred W. McCann, a reporter or writer for the Globe accusing the C.R.B. and many grain manufactures of shipping rotten wheat and flour to Belgium. Also includes some legal documents regarding the investigation of Mr. McCann's charges (Folder 7)
    - Rotten foodstuffs. Consists mainly of correspondence regarding Mr. Alfred W. McCann, a reporter or writer for the Globe accusing the C.R.B. and many grain manufactures of shipping rotten wheat and flour to Belgium. Also includes some legal documents regarding the investigation of Mr. McCann's charges (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - War chests. Correspondence regarding disbursement of funds from various war chests. Includes list of cities that have war chests (Folder 2)
  - Miscellany (Folder 3)
- NEW YORK OFFICE HISTORY FILE, 1915-1922.
  Typescripts, drafts and working materials for an official history of the Commission for Relief in Belgium
  - Typescripts, 1915-1919 (Box 302)
    - "The Commission for Relief in Belgium: A Record of the Founding and Establishment of the Commission, and of Its Operations from October 1914 to July 1915," 1915 (Folder 1)
    - "Commission for Relief in Belgium Benevolence, 1914-1919," 1919 (revised 1927) (Folder 2)
  - Drafts and working materials, 1915-1922
    - General (Folder 3-4)
    - Donations and contributions (Folder 5)
    - Organization Department (Folder 6)
    - Press and Publicity Department (Folder 7)
    - Purchasing Department (Folder 8)
    - State committees. Includes correspondence with former officials of state committees (Folder 9)
- NEW YORK OFFICE LACE DEPARTMENT FILE, 1915-1919
  - General. Correspondence and memoranda, 1915-1917 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Invoice books, 1915-1919
    - No. 1. 1915 May-July (Folder 2)
    - No. 2. 1915 July-December (Folder 3)
    - No. 3. 1915 December-1916 February (Folder 4)
    - No. 4. 1916 February-June (Folder 5)
    - No. 5. 1916 June-October (Folder 6)
    - No. 6. 1916 October-December (Folder 7)
    - No. 7. 1916 December-1917 February (Folder 8)
    - No. 8. 1917 February-May (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - No. 9. 1917 May-August (Folder 2)
    - No. 10. 1917 September-December (Folder 3)
    - No. 11. 1917 December (Folder 4)
    - No. 12. 1917 December-1918 January (Folder 5)
    - No. 13. 1918 January-March (Folder 6)
    - No. 14. 1918 April-June (Folder 7)
    - No. 15. 1918 July-September (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - No. 16. 1918 September (Folder 2)
    - No. 17. 1918 September (Folder 3)
    - No. 18. 1918 September-December (Folder 4)
    - No. 19. 1918 December-1919 January (Folder 5)
    - No. 20. 1919 January-March (Folder 6)
    - No. 21. 1919 March-April (Folder 7)
  - Consignment books, 1915-1919 (Box 306)
    - No. 1. 1915 June-August (Folder 1)
    - No. 2. 1915 August-October (Folder 2)
    - No. 3. 1915 October-November (Folder 3)
    - No. 4. 1915 November (Folder 4)
    - No. 5. 1915 November-December (Folder 5)
    - No. 6. 1915 December-1916 January (Folder 6)
    - No. 7. 1916 January-February (Folder 7)
    - No. 8. 1916 March (Folder 8)
    - No. 9. 1916 March-May (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - No. 10. 1916 May-1917 January (Folder 2)
    - No. 11. 1917 January-April (Folder 3)
    - No. 12. 1917 April-September (Folder 4)
    - No. 13. 1917 September-November (Folder 5)
    - No. 14. 1917 November-December (Folder 6)
    - No. 14½. 1917 November-December (Folder 7)
    - No. 15. 1917 November-1918 February (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - No. 16. 1918 February-July (Folder 2)
    - No. 17. 1918 June (Folder 3)
    - No. 18. 1918 June-July (Folder 4)
    - No. 19. 1918 July (Folder 5)
    - No. 20. 1918 July-October (Folder 6)
    - No. 21. 1918 October-1919 February (Folder 7)
    - No. 22. 1919 February-April (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - Consignment books for Allied Bazaar, 1916-1917
    - No. 1. 1916 June (Folder 2)
    - No. 2. 1916 June-December (Folder 3)
    - No. 3. 1916 December-1917 January (Folder 4)
    - No. 4. 1917 January (Folder 5)
- NEW YORK OFFICE MINUTES, 1915-1918.
  Includes agenda, and financial and other reports received
  - 1915 (Box 310)
    - November (Folder 1)
    - December (Folder 2)
  - 1916
    - January (Folder 3)
    - February (Folder 4)
    - March (Folder 5)
    - April (Folder 6)
    - May (Folder 7)
    - June (Folder 8)
    - July (Folder 9)
    - August (Folder 10)
    - September (Folder 11)
    - October (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - November (Folder 2)
    - December (Folder 3)
  - 1917
    - January (Folder 4)
    - February (Folder 5)
    - March (Folder 6)
    - April (Folder 7)
    - May (Folder 8)
    - June (Folder 9)
    - July (Folder 10)
    - August (Folder 11)
    - September (Folder 12)
    - October (Folder 13)
    - November (Folder 14)
    - December (Folder 15)
  - 1918
    - January (Folder 16)
    - February (Folder 17)
    - March (Folder 18)
    - April (Folder 19)
    - May (Folder 20)
    - June (Folder 21)
    - July (Folder 22)
    - August (Folder 23)
    - September (Folder 24)
    - October (Folder 25)
    - November (Folder 26)
- NEW YORK OFFICE PERSONNEL FILES, 1914-1919
  - General, 1914-1918 (Box 312)
    - Correspondence, 1915-1918 (Folder 1)
    - Membership rosters and lists, 1916-1918 (Folder 2)
    - Member data sheets, 1916-1917 (Folder 3)
    - Candidate lists, n.d. (Folder 4)
    - Candidate data sheets, 1914-1917
      - A-D (Folder 5)
      - E-H (Folder 6)
      - I-W (Folder 7)
    - Miscellany. Lists and notes, 1916-1917 (Folder 8)
  - Individual member files. Correspondence and biographical data, 1914-1919
    - Allen, Ben S., 1918 (Folder 9)
    - Ames, William C., 1916-1918 (Folder 10)
    - Angell, Frank, 1915-1918 (Folder 11)
    - Arrowsmith, Robert. Includes reports, proclamations, clippings and miscellany collected by Arrowsmith (Box 313)
      - 1914-1917 (Folder 1)
      - 1918-1919 (Folder 2)